[{"answer": "We're getting closer, but I'm definitely not going to predict that we are there we have seen these things fall apart and, you know, die several death before they come back to life.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Dana, are we nearly there?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "The key for this moment is going to be 11 A.M. tomorrow morning.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "So how do you see tomorrow shaping up in terms of important key moments?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "I certainly hope so.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Can we genuinely look forward to a deal tomorrow do you think?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "I lay almost all of it at his feet because he's the one who started this.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "How much blame do you lay at the feet of Senator Cruz?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Well, I mean I understand where Peter King is coming from in terms of that frustration but that's really passing the buck.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Was the sheer venom of one Republican on other Republican, what is going on with the GOP right now?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Well, he was definitely a part of it in all that that the challenge of it is not just that there's a shutdown is that something unique did happen.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "So, it's like but am I the most naive person in America or wasn't it the same Senator Cruz that caused the shutdown that led to all this?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, it's just unbelievable that what they're outraged about is not that 800,000 federal employees are furloughed.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "What was your reaction first of all to what he just said?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Well, the sheer nonsensical situation that the guy who caused it standing by the barricades if thing go on.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "I mean the question that should be asked is why did we have to shut the government down in order to make sure that we could find a way to work together on other issues?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, I wrote it really as one mom who happens to serve in Congress.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Very quickly, tell me about the book and what do you think we can learn from this in relation to what's going on right now?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "And we need more women...", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Women, do you think?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "You know, I think we need more women because in my experience in the women in Congress on both sides of the aisle talk about this all the time, how if they just put us in a room together more often, we could solve a lot of these problems.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "It wasn't for all these testosterone alpha males marching around?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "South Africans say yes.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Are these good times for South Africa?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "And when all of that happens, housing markets slows down.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "... what is going on will quite likely lead to significant increases, you know, general cost?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "RMAN: They are playing, as I said before in my opinion, political shenanigans.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "What do you make of the way they're conducting their business in America's name?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Well, if we hadn't just been coming out of one of the most major devastations to the United States, 2008, 2009, and so forth, maybe there would have been time to plan for this but many people, Piers, were out of work to no fault of their own truthfully, we totally shrank during those years and now they were just getting back on their feet again.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Whatever your income may be?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Most likely, every time they get a paycheck, if they could automatically pay themselves first, you know, most people, the truth of the matter is they don't have any money.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Should they do it weekly, monthly, how should they do it in a most effective way to capitalize on that income?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Truthfully if I had an answer for that right now I probably would be President of the United States.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "What can America do as a nation to tackle those two huge hydrous which are dominating the economic landscape?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "You have a few months here to get your act together.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "So, what is your message to them going forward?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Well, Piers we pick that date because the gun prohibition lobby was planning on accelerating and launching their new attacks on 80 million law abiding firearms owners, firearm civil rights.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Why did you think the December the 14th would be a good day to show Americans a good side to guns Mr. Gottlieb?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Because that's totally over the top, that's not what our intent was, that's not what -- we were going to do was.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Why you -- why you laughing?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Piers how dare the anti-gun movement I've been using this tragedy all year long...", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "How dare you?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Hey, my heart goes after them.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "How dare you?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "I won't back off...", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "70?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "...people like you.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "80 times?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Mr. Gottlieb, you're misquoting it.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "...why shouldn't anybody else?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Because your definition of gun safety is banning guns and confiscating guns.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "I said that I will use that day to promote gun safety on behalf of those families, which part of that sentence do you find offensive?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Well, actually if you read the reports today, the...", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "How many gun murders we have a year in Britain Mr. Gottlieb?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "...the only important in Britain -- well, one of the promises that...", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "How many gun murders a year?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Well, guess what...", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "And you know the reason?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "I think that would be a good thing, yes.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "You want less Americans to own guns period, right?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "But look, there's so many people everyday saved their lives because of gun...", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Do you remember the last time we had an interview together?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Do you remember the last time you came on my show?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "It was right after the Newtown.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "What day was that?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Houston.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Houston, do you read?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think there's many people out there that want to do that, Piers.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "How do we get past this notion that you have to celebrate the anniversary of Sandy Hook with pro-gun campaign?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "It is ridiculous.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Gabby and I went to see that about a week ago, Piers.", "docId": "131014pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Captain Kelly, have you seen \"Gravity\", what do you make of it?", "qSentId": 645}]